Hire Brands is a house of brands. We
have our most known brand which is Heer
which started off as a subscription box
and an online head shop. Our goal with
the subscription box was to give our
customers a new glass piece every month.
From there we got into the manufacturing
game under Har Supply where we're
producing roughly 100 million pre-o
cones a month. When I came on board our
operations were based out of New York.
We had a whole fulfillment center there
being run by one of the partners' family
members. When we were trying to get
things done, we had no real transparency
what was going on. We were trying to
figure out, did we have enough
inventory? You know, was inventory being
shipped out in time, how many boxes were
being produced? We had no KPIs or
metrics to try to figure out how to
scale the business and understand how we
were receiving anything. The software
they were using didn't have good
batching, didn't have good routing, no
order splits. They didn't really care to
try to understand how our subscription
boxes needed to be packed. They didn't
care how those need to be produced,
shipping label, print management, none
of it. I knew I needed to find a
software that was very flexible, very
agile. I came across a Phil, did an
onboarding call. We're getting closer to
Black Friday, Cyber Monday. We started
printing out labels. The batching
process was great. The support that we
had during our onboarding time was
amazing. When I moved to the wholesale
fulfillments coordinator, the position
was a team of about six people that were
in charge of operating the entirety of
Fulfill while all of the associates were
handling a paperbased system. marking
things with a highlighter, marking
things with pens. I've dealt with other
picking systems. You would have to put
the cart in the middle and you would
just be going around in circles and
circles, which it just takes more time.
The way Fulfills has it set up is that
when it comes in, we scan the location,
it throws you in alphabetical order. So,
when we're picking it won't throw you
across the whole warehouse. We did not
have those batching systems anywhere
else. It makes all the orders come in
really, really organized. Over the
course of about six months, we brought
the wholesale department to two members
fully on computers, roughly one or two
pickers that were using the digital
guns. My team at the time went from
finishing 10 to 15 orders in a day to
about 40 or 50. We've been able to
streamline the process with fulfill from
a sales order being developed to
purchase requests being done and a draft
PO being generated within a matter of
seconds. They were spending about 12
hours per transaction to run through
that whole process. Now that process
gets done with less than 15 minutes
worth of work. We have a promise to our
customers to get every order out between
24 hours or 48 hours. And we wouldn't be
able to do that without fulfill orders.
Once upon a time would take anywhere
between like a week to 2 weeks. Ended up
being like 3 days at most when it was
like 1,200 items. When we first got
onboarded and you know they built you
know all the return stuff. We've
streamlined that process from days
lagging behind on dealing with returns
to probably within 30 minutes a day.
We've been able to develop data
warehousing reports using all the data
warehouse modules, reports that
literally tell us how much inventory to
reorder. We use the forecasting modules
and fulfill and they've been able to
develop to understand our industry even
better. It's allowed us to have better
inventory controls on our subscription
boxes. So instead of us sitting there
and building a,000 subscription boxes or
5,000 or 20,000 in one day, we're
developing and producing them based on
the actual orders that have come
through, I have it pushing into Google
Sheets for a lot of our reports that we
share with a lot of our customers to let
them know how much stock they have of
their own product here or how much stock
we have of our own product. And that's
been one of the things that allow us to
scale a lot quicker now with our PRO co
manufacturing is just that aspect. This
summer we use Fulfill's API integrations
into a Google sheet document to see how
we're doing on inventory, how we're
doing on sales, how we're doing with
like stock intervals. We've been able to
use the information from fulfill across
APIs like Slack and ClickUp to look at
certain purchase orders or look at
certain inventory movements. Now that
there is a native Slack integration,
it's allowed us to have more realtime
information passed via Slack. Now, when
an order is processed, instead of
finance having to wait for a
notification, they're being notified
directly in Slack like, "Hey, this order
was processed. Go ahead and book revenue
right now." That's one of the features
we're probably going to use a lot more
going into the year. Speed to market
super important for us. The production
module is going to allow us to have
full-on transparency on what's being
developed and produced and how we can
actually further the business, right?
How we can invest more time, how we can
speed things up. We're using the drop
shipment function within Fulfill to
create a purchase request. That purchase
request turns into a draft purchase
order. Then we go to the drop shipment,
fulfill it. I'm saving hours and days
worth of time to take on more business.
Fulfill has seen plenty of transactions,
plenty of different businesses,
different sizes, different models.
They've been able to service us in every
way possible.